junocloud.me 2014-12-03

# JunoCloud.me - Remote Storage Sevice

We, www.junocloud.me, are committed to protecting, respecting and safeguarding the privacy of the visitors to this website. This policy outlines out how we will treat your personal information.

Please be informed that this website uses cookies. By using this website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy as these are outlined below.

What information do we collect from visitors: 

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information

  (a) Any information that you provide by filling in any of the forms to be found on the www.junocloud.me website (“the Site”). This includes but is not limited to personal contact details, contact telephone numbers and any other information submitted when registering with us and/or creating an account with us;

  (b) Information may also be collected when you choose to complete customer surveys, provide us with feedback or choose to participate in competitions and/or special promotions;

  (c) Information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation);

  (d) Information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of any of our services);

  (e) Information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services such as email notifications and/or newsletters;

  (f) Information on any correspondence between us in case you choose to contact us.

  (g) Information is also collected using cookies.

Cookies

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on this website. Session cookies are used to keep track of you whilst you navigate this website; and persistent cookies are used to enable our website to recognise you when you visit; 

Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.

The use of cookies enables us to analyse the use of this website by generating statistical and other information about it.

Should you wish to opt-in to this service, our advertisers may also send you cookies. If you utilise the opt-out mechanism, which uses a cookie, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you might need to use a browser plug-in if available.

Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites - including this one.

Using your personal information and information about your contacts

Personal information submitted to us via this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

  (a) administer this website;

  (b) improve your browsing experience by personalising this website;

  (c) enable your use of the services available on the website;

  (d) supply to you services purchased via the website;

  (e) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;

  (f) send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;

  (g) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;

  (h) send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar electronic technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);

  (i) provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;

  (j) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to your use of the website;

  (k) to carry out market analysis and research;

  (l) Ensure that you are complying with the terms and conditions of use and to comply with our statutory.

We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

All our website financial transactions are handled through our secure payment services providers. We will share information with these secure payment services providers only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments.

We also might need to collect information about others. This in cases where some of the features on this website allow you to share the content which you upload with other people. 

Disclosures

We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose your personal information: 

  (a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

  (b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

  (c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);

  (d) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling; and 

  (e) to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

Marketing and other uses of your non-personal data by us and by 3rd parties

We may share non-personal information we collect under any of the above-mentioned circumstances. We may share these with other companies within our group or other 3rd parties to develop targeted advertising to you, or to help us prepare or share aggregate business and marketing reports.

We would also like to send you information about services offered by us and selected 3rd parties that we thing they might be of interest to you. For this purpose your e-mail address, which you have provided, might be used.

If you do not want your data to be used in this way, or your details to be passed on to 3rd parties for marketing purposes, not to use your personal information, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please inform us know by e-mailing us at [support@junocloud.me](mailto:support@junocloud.me).

International data transfers

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

Information that you provide may be transferred to countries whose data protection laws might be lacking.

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

Security of your personal information

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

We undertake to store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology.

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to the website).

Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. 

Your rights

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information will be subject to:

  (a) the payment of an administrative fee (currently fixed at EUR 50.00); and

  (b) the supply of appropriate evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we will usually accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a solicitor or bank plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your current address).

We may withhold such personal information to the extent permitted by law.

Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

Updating information

Please let us know if the personal information that, we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please write to us by email to [support@junocloud.me](mailto:support@junocloud.me).
